Oh my god. Thank you. Make noise for you
for leaving your house tonight.
[cheering] Oh my god. You did it.
[applause] And I love I love to see
beautiful women out here tonight.
[cheering] Make noise. Every woman here,
my sleepy, sleepy queens, make noise for
them. Make it and [cheering] make it
really loud for them because they will
fall asleep. So keep screaming, okay?
They will because they're all smiling,
but it's a lie. Okay, every woman in
here can't wait to go home. Every woman,
they're counting down the minutes till
bedtime. Every woman, trust me, so am I.
Okay, [laughter] you think I want to be
here right now? This is my job. At least
you guys are out having fun. This is a
cubicle to me. Okay, this is not
[laughter] Do you know what I mean?
Every woman here waiting till bedtime
counting down. You're mad at me cuz I'm
keeping you from your bedtime. You're so
This is [laughter] I know that most of
the women here, for real, you laid your
PJs out on your bed before you left the
house, didn't you? That's how much you
love bedtime. That's how you love
bedtime so much. You planned your outfit
already. [laughter] That's how much you
love it. And you laid it on your on your
bed all dramatic. You folded it like,
"Mama's got to laugh. I'll be right
back. Mama's got to laugh." You
[laughter] know, you can't wait. Can't
wait to go home. But I'm so glad. I love
seeing women out having fun. You know
what I mean? Live your life. Enjoy your
night. It makes me so happy. It's just
women, we're very smart and we have a
very uh we have a complicated
relationship with fun. You know, we none
of us want to have fun. Okay, we need to
have fun. [laughter] There's a
difference, right? So, we know that fun
is healthy for us. It's good for us. So,
we plan fun. [laughter]
Women, women, we schedule fun. We
schedule fun weeks and months in
advance. Really far in advance. Some of
you, for real, you have a brunch
scheduled for Q4, don't you? You do. And
y'all, how excited? You know what I
mean? And and you're you can't wait. And
this is how this is how women show love
to each other. This is something we say
with enthusiasm. We text each other [\h__\h]
like IT'S IN THE CALENDAR. IT'S IN THE
CALENDAR, [\h__\h] [screaming]
I CAN'T WAIT. YOU KNOW, [laughter]
you love it. You love it. You got to
plan your fun, but it's um you schedule
it too far. Too far away. It's too far
away. So what happens is weeks pass,
months pass and then the day for fun
arrives like today [laughter]
and you kind of don't want to go and I
KNOW YOU ALL FOUGHT to come here. I know
you did. You kind of don't want to go.
So but you know that fun is healthy for
you. So you got to commit. You're smart
and you're healthy. You committed to the
fun. So you got to start the process of
uh lying. You got to lie. You lie to
your friends. You lied to each other all
day. You all text each other lies like
I'm EXCITED FOR THE SHOW. YOU EXCITED?
Should we do dinner before or after?
You're trying to like lock in
supplemental plans to make sure this
[laughter] [\h__\h] happens. You know, you
got to confirm.
I think there's a friend in every friend
group who uh they start that text chain
about 24 hours before the fun plans. You
know, about 24 hours ahead, they go
looping everyone in. Looping in.
[laughter] Like, are we on? Are we on
for tomorrow? Are we on? That's the
friend that needs this the most.
[laughter] Okay, so don't bail on that
friend. Okay, don't she needs this [\h__\h]
dude. That's Are we on? Cuz what she's
really saying with that text message is
it's not are we on, it's don't bail on
me, [\h__\h] YOU HAVE NO IDEA THE KIND of
week I had. DON'T YOU BAIL ON ME, [\h__\h]
Are we on? I'll see you at the show.
I'll pick you up. What are you wearing?
[laughter]
What are you wearing? Show me your
outfit so I know you're [\h__\h] going to
the show. Okay. I don't know.
It's so much lying. You got to lie. You
got to lie to each other. And the
hardest part is the lies you tell
yourself, you know, cuz you have to hype
yourself up to come out to the show.
It's It's hard to commit to the fun. And
I know a lot of you, you laid in bed
today and some of you had to uh look up
my little Tik Tok videos today, didn't
you? Didn't you? It's like listening to
the band the day of the concert. You
know what I mean? You want to like hype
yourself up for the show. You know what
I mean? cuz you planned this so long ago
you forgot, you know? [laughter]
So you looked at my little videos,
you're like, "How funny is this [\h__\h]
[laughter]
Like, how much do I like this [\h__\h] I
got to put on pants and call an Uber for
their shit." You know what I mean? It's
[laughter] exhausting. Cuz it's not your
fault. You planned this so long ago. So
long ago that you forgot that I'm funny.
You had to remind yourself if I'm funny,
which I am. [laughter] And after
tonight, you'll never forget. OKAY?
[screaming] NEVER. NEVER.
>> [applause]
>> WHERE ARE THE SINGLE PEOPLE AT? Single
people. Okay. Amazing. Love it. You're
out. That's fun. So, that means everyone
else is couples. Is that what that
means? Where where are like the couples,
relationships, people on dates, everyone
else? All right. [applause] All right.
Relax.
You're not better than them. You know
what [laughter] I mean? I don't like the
pretentiousness. Couples are always a
little have a little attitude, a little
pretentious. They're always rubbing.
Always rubbing his legs. Legs.
[laughter] pretentious tri triggering
me. You know what I mean? It's just so
aggressive. There's a couple like every
city, every show that every there's
always a couple that's like 21 years.
I'm [laughter] like, no one asked. Okay,
congrats. You know, you know, cuz
because single people don't do that. Do
you ever see [laughter]
a single person walking around bragging
about their timeline? Do you ever see a
sing [laughter] just single people
walking around like FOUR YEARS STRONG?
YOU KNOW, YOU KNOW, the holidays are
rough, but I love myself. I love myself.
[laughter] Don't worry about me. You
know,
single people, I would argue, are the
most oppressed group in society. Okay?
This spans every race, gender,
everything. Single adults get
disrespected by couples every day. And
the couples, you'll play innocent like
you you don't know what you do. Okay? Th
This is how I learned this the hard way.
Let's say uh you guys go on a vacation
with all your friends. There are singles
and couples. You guys rent a big house
somewhere, Airbnb.
Let's talk sleeping arrangements.
[laughter]
Where do the couples make the single
people sleep?
Couch. Couch. Couch. Did you hear those
broken voices? [laughter] Those are
those. The couch. The couch. Couch.
ONE TIME AT A SHOW, someone said the
porch. The porch. [laughter]
Okay, you guys think single people don't
have bones? You think cuz they have no
one to hold at night. They don't deserve
a mattress. Like they don't deserve a
duvet, anything, a comforter. They're
human beings just like you. Okay?
[laughter] They deserve a real bed. A
real bed, not a bunk bed. Okay? A real
bed. Dude, as a single woman, I have
slept on more bunk beds [laughter] as an
adult single woman than I ever have as a
child. You [laughter] understand?
I'm a grown woman with selfrespect. And
you want me to climb a little [laughter]
ladder to reach my slumber? I have to
engage my core at 1000 p.m. [laughter] I
have to I have to parkour out of my bed
every morning on my vacation. I'm just
Spider-Man all over Palm Springs.
[laughter]
I took off work for this dude.
You guys, you have no idea the the
miscellaneous objects and furniture that
I've slept on. It's like the the objects
I've slept on, it gives me more trauma
than the men that I've slept. Does that
make sense? Oh, [laughter]
you know, you guys know what um you know
what a love seat is? You know those tiny
couches? Those little baby couch.
They're only big enough for a couple to
cuddle and hold hands [laughter] or one
person to cry. Okay. I've slept I've
slept on love seats. Uh you guys have no
idea. [laughter]
Uh an ottoman.
Do you guys you guys know ottomans? You
[laughter] guys [\h__\h] with ottomans? I
slept
on an ottoman at the foot of a bed at
the I was so close. Right there. So
close. No cigar. [laughter] It was right
there. And it was touching the bed. It
was a beautiful king-size bed.
Beautiful. [laughter] Where a couple
slept. You know, these [\h__\h] claimed
to be my friends, but they made me sleep
perpendicular to them [laughter]
all weekend. All weekend on an ottoman.
like a mediumsized dog. I slept
[laughter]
all like on and I was a good girl all
weekend. I was a good girl. I didn't
cause a fuss, you know. But sometimes I
I try to reach out and touch the bed and
THEY'D BE LIKE, "NO, BAD. ONLY GIRL.
SETTLE. SETTLE." They kicked me. They
kicked me to sleep [laughter]
cuz I was alone. Okay. A
It's not right, dude. Cuz it's like
these trips, they're messed up, right?
Because when it's all over, what do you
all do about the cost? You split it. You
split it down the middle. Do you know
how triggering that is to your single
friends to get that Venmo request? You
know, cuz it's like, okay, the couples
you guys got you slept in a private
casita, you know, [laughter] with a
balcony in a jacuzzi, but I slept on a
rocking horse in the garage. [laughter]
Okay.
Four nights [laughter] like this. $600.
Okay. Okay.
I'm happy for the single people that are
here. I'm excited for you. I do think
it's exciting cuz single people, where
are you again? You're everywhere, right?
Like, [cheering] okay, good for you. But
isn't it exciting to be single and go
out? You know what I mean? Isn't it fun?
Cuz it's kind of like you never know.
You know, you could meet someone.
[laughter]
It's probably not tonight. It's uh I
don't mean to bum you out. It's it's a
you deserve love. It's just a numbers
game. You know what I mean? Like
statistically, what are the odds? You're
going to meet the love of your life
tonight. No, [laughter] it's not. I
don't even know you and I'd bet money on
it. It's not tonight. It's not tonight.
Just let it go. This is your night. This
is it. Accept it. This is it. You're
going to laugh. You're going to enjoy
the show. Then you're going to go home
and swipe and sigh until you pass out.
And that's I'm [laughter]
I'm not even doing comedy anymore. I'm
just I'm just making everyone all the
single people sad. like you're alone and
it's time to accept that. All right,
[laughter] stop it.
It's just
it is too much pressure because if
you're single, it just that all that
means is your perfect person could be
anywhere at any moment. So, it's too
much pressure. It's like every time you
leave your house, you got to be a little
alert always. No matter where you are,
you go outside and you just have to be
like,
[laughter]
you know, no matter even if you're at
Chipotle, you're like, [laughter] "Oh,
oops. I dropped my
you want to look that'll be a little
extra." You know, [laughter]
that's your life. You're laugh. Yeah.
that it's just embarrassing the pro the
whole process of being single cuz you
have all the it's like you have to go
outside in the world and like present
your body to everyone. It's
embarrassing. We're all grown adults but
we go outside like
[laughter]
anyone [laughter]
maybe for you. No. No. Do you like No.
Okay. No. Okay. Sorry. You know
[laughter] it's just
I feel bad. I don't I don't want to
tease too much. Being single is it's
amazing. It It's awesome. There's
freedom, independence. It just sometimes
gets lonely. So, you want to be around
people. You want to go out to a comedy
show or to a bar. I don't know why we do
that. You know how dangerous that you're
lonely and you go to a bar. You know
what you're do. You're going to the
grocery store hungry.
You know, you know that's bad, right?
You're going to bring home something you
regret, [laughter] right? You're going
to wake up in the morning and be like,
"Why did I put that inside me? Why?
I ate too much." [laughter]
I think out of all the out of all the
phases of like love dating, if it makes
anyone feel better, I think it all
equally sucks. You know what I mean?
It's grass is greener. Everyone has
their problems. But my my least favorite
phase of of dating is like the very new
phase when you're not officially a
couple yet. you know, when it's you're
you're very new to each other. So,
because that's the phase where you have
to be like down for whatever, [laughter]
you know what I mean? You have to be
chill. You have to like, you know what I
mean? And it's just like that's not it's
like everything cuz you can't like plan
too much, right? Like especially the
first sleepover you have with someone
new. You can't plan that. You can't
schedule you can't send them a calendar
invite for that, you know, like [\h__\h] it
and sucking Friday at 9:00. I'll see you
there. You know, you can't [laughter]
You got to be easy, Bri. You let it
happen. You have to let it happen. So,
you have to dance around it. You You use
code, whatever. Netflix and chill or
like, you know, movie night. Like my
place. Movie night. I'm like, sure.
Yeah. [laughter]
Okay. Movie night. Okay.
Sorry. I don't know why there's two, by
the way. Like, OKAY. [screaming]
YEAH. Movie night. It's like [laughter]
It's like let's be adults, right? It's a
sleepover. It's a sleepover. Let's call
it what it is. But I'm a woman. You know
what I mean? Like, I can't just like
pass out anywhere. What am I, 12? I
can't just wake up on some dude's couch
and be like, "Oh, did I pass out here
last night?" And like skateboard away
with my [laughter] like
my capri son. Like, no. I'm a woman. I'm
a grown woman. And you know what that
means? I have a 14step nighttime
routine, [laughter] right? And those
creams come with me wherever the [\h__\h] I
go. Okay? So, I got to know, are we
doing this or not? I need my creams.
Okay. [laughter] You can't take me to a
new location without time to bring my
stuff. That's not a date. That's a
kidnapping, [\h__\h] [laughter] Are
I got to know, are we doing this or not?
I want to know where am I at tonight.
Are we do [laughter] like I want a
confirmation email. Okay. Like, are we
going to do this or not, dude? That's
how I flirt, by the way. That's like,
dude, are we GOING TO GO? LET'S GO,
DUDE. HE'S LIKE TRYING TO fight or [\h__\h]
me. Like, why are you screaming at me?
>> [laughter]
>> Okay.
But uh I do uh I I know I know how this
goes down. Whenever I have a first
sleepover, I I know what's going to
happen. So I prepare. I pack a You guys
don't know we do this, but uh we pack a
secret overnight bag sometimes and it's
a tiny secret TSA ass bag that we sneak
into. It's like we are smuggling in
floss to your shitty apartment
[laughter] just hiding it from you. You
know, like we're the ones embarrassed
like you don't have any [\h__\h] towels,
but we're embarrassed. you know, we're
bringing [laughter]
this secret floss
to your shitty studio. We're like, uh,
you know what I mean? We're hiding it
from you because it's like, we can't let
you see it too soon, right? You know
what I mean? It is I think our overnight
bag, it is it's like the condom for you
guys. You know, we want you to bring it.
We want you to come over prepared. We
like that. But if you show it to us too
soon, [laughter]
it just kills the vibe. You know what I
mean? Like we can't. We're just like,
"Wow, really? Really? Wow." Like I did
shave for this, but wow. Really, dude?
Really? [laughter] Like I am down, but
wow, dude. Seriously? Wow.
But [laughter]
thank you, sir.
I do. I I think there's like the weird
phenomenon with getting ready for bed.
I've noticed that, you know, the very
first time you get ready for bed in
front of a new person, I have never felt
more vulnerable in that moment. There's
something so intimate about taking off
your makeup for the first time in front
of someone new. And we never do that the
first sleepover. That's like 10
sleepover stuff. You got to earn the
right. You got to [\h__\h] your way to the
bathroom sink [laughter] to earn the
right. I have to earn it to to take off
my bronzer in front of these jabronies.
I'm working so hard to that. So, I don't
know why. Why is that the levels of
intimacy? Like, why why does it have to
go penetration exfoliation? [laughter]
Like, why do you guys do that to just
let us get ready for bed? It's our right
as women. This is our we need to march
in the streets and protest, you know,
with our myicellar water. We should
splash it around. Splash it around on
their face. [laughter]
And none of the guys even know what I
just said, by the way. They have no
idea. Myellar water. They're like, "My
cellar? What kind of water is that? Is
[laughter]
is there protein in it? I'll I'll try it
if it's How are the macros on that? I'll
try it. Yeah. No, it's not. [laughter] I
think you guys don't. Myellar water is
something that takes off your makeup.
Okay. And I think some of you don't know
how good it feels to take off your
makeup after a long day. It's such a
like sweet release. It's like I get
postnut clarity after I take off my
makeup. Do you [laughter]
I feel like the guys really they're
like, "Oh, bet. Thank you for explaining
it. That's very like I'm trying to get
you here with me. [laughter] Okay. It
feels so just you're giving us blue
balls in our face. Do you understand?
It's hurtful. Does [laughter] that track
I don't know. I don't know. I just I I
think we we got to fix this issue. I
think I know how to do this. Let's just
make getting ready for bed. Let's make
it sexy. You know, like let's make it
part of the foreplay. No, let's do it
together. [laughter] You help me. Come
over here. Help me get ready for bed,
baby. Come over here. You know what I
mean? like take off my bra and my brows,
you know what I [laughter] mean?
Whoops.
Oops. Oh my god. You know, like say
[laughter]
and say say cute stuff to us when you
see that they're shaped differently.
[laughter] You know, you're like, "Oh,
girl, I didn't I didn't realize they're
sisters, not twins. Girl, come over
here." You know, it's [laughter] it's
cute. You know,
[laughter]
I'm 38. I'm never been married. I'm
scared to get married. Are there married
people here?
[applause]
Awesome. Awesome. [laughter] You didn't
really sell it. You didn't I not excited
at all. Uh, [laughter]
no, but I I'm I'm scar I'm scared to do
it because I know it's hard work. I I I
see it the the the only way I see
marriage that the closest thing I've
seen to it is my parents. That's my my
biggest example of marriage. My parents
are still married. They're still
together. They've been married for I
want to say a hundred years. [laughter]
Uh that's how they act at least. Okay. I
think they're like 500 years old. Nobody
knows how old they are. They're very
old. I think they met in like the Han
Dynasty or [laughter] something. I don't
know cuz I asked my dad I asked my dad
how they met and he forgot.
He just [laughter]
he just grunted and walked out of the
room. I was like what a beautiful story
I'll take with me and share. You know
it's like
but for real they they've been married
um this year it will be 50 years. 50
years. Yeah. Right. [applause]
It is incredible. Incredible. 50 years
because, you know, on one hand, it's so
sweet. It's so romantic. You want to
spend that much of your life with one
person. On the other hand, that's 50
years.
50 years. I'm still grappling like how
much time I'm trying to get a
perspective. That amount of time like
freaks me out. 50 years. I'm thinking
about it a lot cuz it's like it's not so
much the years, it's the days.
Do you know what I mean? It's the
[laughter] days. Think about 50 years in
days, dude. 18,000
days. [laughter]
No one's clapping for that, right? Why
would you? That's
[laughter] It's too much time, dude. How
much do you need to learn about one
person? It's too much time. Like, my
parents know too much about each other.
Every dumb little fact. It's like my mom
told me something recently. She was
like, "You know something about your
father is if he ever falls asleep
downstairs in the living room, that
means he had a stressful day. But if he
makes it all the way upstairs to the
bedroom, that means he's relaxed."
[laughter]
And he never told me that.
I learned that on my own. [laughter]
LIKE, "MOM, YOU'RE SICK. THIS IS SICK.
YOU'RE YOU HAVE TO GO OUTSIDE. IS THIS
MARRIAGE? Is this marriage? Is that Is
that all it is? You just sit around and
stare at each other all day and just
observe their every dumb boring habit.
You just like you're just like AI
collecting [laughter] useless data like
you know you just you just watch them
fall asleep like yeah typical go to
sleep [\h__\h] go to sleep [laughter]
typical yeah you're a sleepy guy aren't
you? You know what I mean? That's is
that love? I don't understand it.
[laughter]
50 years I do look up to them cuz it's
like they must have done something
right. So when they talk about their
marriage, I really try to pay attention.
And uh I have learned from them that no
matter how long it's been with the same
person, the marriage does evolve over
time. Cuz my mom said, she's like, "Even
though I've been with your father for
nearly half my life, every day I learn
something new about him that I don't
like." [laughter]
And she's just like 18,000 days. She's
like marking the wall like a [laughter]
prison. $18 a day every day. I was like,
"Fuck
the [\h__\h] [laughter]
It's just scary." So like the married
people here, do you recommend it
[applause and cheering] for real? What
do you love about it?
Whoops. Okay. [laughter]
They're like,
>> "Are you safe? Are you okay?" [laughter]
Okay. You're okay.
I'm straight.
[laughter]
>> Wow. Wow. I don't know why you would
clap for that. It's nothing to It's
nothing to applaud. [laughter]
I didn't do the I didn't want this. It's
not a choice, right ladies? It's not a
[laughter] choice, right? It is
certainly not a choice. I was born this
way. It's a condition many women are
born with. There is no cure. You just
have to slowly accept it over your life.
Okay? It is. None of us wanted this,
fellas. I want you to just reminder none
of us wanted this. Okay, where are the
straight women here?
[cheering and applause]
Hear how sad they are? [laughter]
See how sad they are inside? See how
like none of us wished for this as
little girls? You know what I mean? None
of us as little girls were like, "I
can't wait to grow up and go to a
brewery and talk about his favorite
Batman. I can't Oh. Oh, really? Robert
Patson? That's interesting. I didn't
think you would be. Oh, well, really,
REALLY. [laughter]
It is my truth. I'm straight. I love
men. I truly mean that. I love you guys.
I think you're incredible people.
Really? For real. Where are my straight
boys at tonight? WHERE ARE YOU AT? YEAH.
YEAH. YES. [cheering]
YEAH. YEAH. YOU HEAR THAT? Do you hear
that? Confidence
for no reason. [laughter] JUST YEAH.
[screaming]
FOR WHAT? FOR WHAT? It's like I MATCHED
MY HAT WITH MY PANTS TODAY. YES, you
did. Yes, you did, sweetie. Very good.
Very good. You [cheering] did. It's just
It's beautiful this confidence. I cuz I
I want you all to appreciate how
confident you are. It's a beautiful
thing. I want you to love yourself as
much as I do.
You are so confident. Do you realize
every day you wake up hard? [laughter]
Yes. Yes. Every day. Don't lie. Every
day. Every day. Christmas day.
[laughter]
Your mom's birthday.
Every day.
The day the fire started. [laughter]
January 6th.
[laughter] It's not your fault. You
didn't know. But you woke up a proud boy
that morning, didn't you? YES, YOU DID.
LOVE YOURS. YOU'RE CLAPPING FOR YOUR OWN
DICK. LOOK AT THAT. YES. LOVE YOURSELF.
It's beautiful. You know what I mean?
Every single day every day. And make
make noise, fellas, if this morning.
YEAH. THIS MORNING. YEAH. YOU WOKE UP.
YOU WOKE UP. CARPEY DM, DUDE. YEAH.
It's beautiful, isn't it? Amazing. I
feel like half of the guys here are
totally lying. Like, you know, there's
always a girl who nudges her guy at a
show like, "BABE, RAISE YOUR HAND. WAIT,
make noise. Remember I was there.
Remember it was [laughter]
it was rock hard. I was like, "Not now.
How could you possibly think this is a
good time?" You know, [laughter]
I love I love that about you guys. I
want you to appreciate how confident you
are cuz I that this is what that means.
That means like even in your sleep, even
when you're like half awake in bed,
you're like,
[laughter]
got to get it ready just in case.
Just in case someone's down. It's like
no one's down. [laughter] You know what
I mean? It's 7:00 a.m. on a Tuesday.
Like, you know what I mean? Like, go to
work. [laughter]
It's just crazy. But you know why? You
know why I like that joke?
Tomorrow morning when it happens to you,
[laughter]
you're all going to think of my face.
THIS. LOOK AT IT. LOOK AT IT. LOOK AT
ME. WHERE'S THE CAMERA? LOOK AT IT.
REMEMBER THIS. Remember this. You're
going to think of this. And it will go
down quickly. But [laughter] it's going
to be a fun moment we all share
together. You guys are all blood
brothers for life for the rest of this.
[laughter]
# blood brothers. The name of the
special actually. BLOOD.
UM, to me, straight guys, you're all the
same, you know? It's like every
[laughter]
every straight guy here is you're just a
silly boy. You're silly. You're fun.
You're goofy. You have an amazing
attitude. I I always have fun with you.
You're very positive people. Um, I love
your sense of humor. I love your sense
of humor because your sense of humor, it
never develops. [laughter]
It's the same [\h__\h] you laughed at in
junior high. Like [\h__\h] slaps today.
It's the same [\h__\h] No matter how old
you grow, I've seen grown men, no matter
what. Grown men, father of three, 401k,
poo poo pee pee. Haha.
[laughter] Okay.
Never change cuz you can't. But I just I
love to watch men grow laterally. It's a
fun journey. [laughter]
Interesting. You're funny. I like to
observe you guys, too. I like to watch
you live your everyday life, but you do
you do things that uh confuse me a lot.
I see a lot of men uh spit on the
sidewalk all the time. Why is that?
[laughter] Why? Why? Why do you do that?
Is it I is it is it to assert dominance
over [laughter] I don't know over your
local Walgreens? They're like what what
what is it for? Is it just do you know
what you look like in the mornings?
You're just like [laughter] you're just
like rock hard like
like the sun is rising behind you. I'm
like it's just a lot. It's a big sight
in the morning, you [laughter] know? But
I feel okay. I feel bad. I'm teasing you
too much. I feel bad. I feel bad cuz I
love men. I don't want I don't want to
generalize. Obviously, I know for a fact
not all men spit on the sidewalk,
but all spit on the sidewalk
is from a man. [laughter] Right.
[cheering] Right.
Confucious say, [laughter]
no one googled that. I don't know.
[laughter]
Nobody. Okay. There's one thing men do
that I don't think um I think you guys
could use improvement on. I don't think
men are the best at texting. Okay. Men
know text good. See how they heard that?
You see how they [laughter] I'm trying
to get you guys to Okay. I I only know
this because I'm on a text chain with
only straight men. That's how I Is
everyone Anyone here on a text chain
with only straight men? You must. It's a
horrifying place to [laughter] be an all
straight guy text chain. It is
horrifying cuz it's it's a lot of chaos
in these text chains. Cuz this is the
trick. This is how these chains work.
You guys talk a lot but not to each
other. [laughter]
You know, you just
talk, you know, it's like whatever's on
your mind. It's like meme real gift the
score. It's like whatever. It's it's
like an unregulated Reddit thread. It's
just whatever the I'm like, who started
this? Are you guys even friends?
[laughter] You know what I mean? It's a
scary place. It's very scary because I'm
I'm on one of these text chains with my
guy friends and like they send the
scariest stuff when I'm never ready. One
of my one of my buddies Paul, he texted
this in the chain unprompted out of
nowhere and I memorized it for you all.
Okay. He said, he said, uh, the toilet
is the amplifier
[laughter]
for the electric guitar string. That is
the fart from [snorts] my butt.
[laughter]
Wow, look at all these straight guys
clap. Applause break for that. I've been
talking for 40 minutes, you [\h__\h] He
claps for a straight guy's text that I
quoted. [laughter]
The toilet.
The toilet is the amplifier. Let's all
say it together as a class. The toilet
is the amplifier
for the ELECTRIC GUITAR STRING. That is
the fart from my butt. Yay. [music]
Very good. Very good. Snaps. Yes.
Straight snaps.
[laughter]
9:00 a.m. I got that text message. It
was 9:00 a.m. I was in a meeting and I
had to pretend I didn't read that
horseshit [laughter] text message. I was
livid, filled with rage, furious. I
couldn't focus all day. I couldn't stop
thinking about this text [laughter] all
day cuz it is it is beautifully written.
If you think about it, it's honestly
there's it's poetic. There's no fat on
that text. It's beautiful. The toilet is
the amplifier. [laughter]
The toilet does amplify the fart. It's
like an ally for the fart. You know what
I mean? It's It gives the fart a safe
space
to be unapologetically that [laughter]
it's beautiful. But 9:00 a.m. 9:00 a.m.
I get texts like that. I don't why cuz
it's like why why couldn't he just have
said good morning? [laughter] Why didn't
he just say good morning? Good morning.
But no, he just he had to share his
little poo poo haiku with the group
[laughter] cuz he's a silly boy. He
couldn't help it. You guys are silly
boys.
>> [laughter]
>> very silly at 9:00 a.m.
But this is how I know. I think you guys
do have a language, a secret language
with each other. Cuz if one of your
buddies in the chain out of nowhere just
texted you, "Good morning," then the
rest of you would have sidebarred on a
different chain and been like, "Dude, is
Paul okay?" What's wrong with Paul? He's
not zany today. Is he all right?
[laughter]
I'm currently I'm no longer single. I
I'm with man. [laughter] I'm
Oh, wow. Thank you. Yeah, I have a man.
I got a man. I did. I got a man. And
that's very nice when people clap for
that. I don't know. That's always the
reaction. Everyone's like applauding and
cheering and it's uh like one one time
at a show a girl came up to me and she
called me an inspiration,
[laughter] right? Just for getting a
boyfriend.
That's how hard it is in the streets,
right? Just to get a boyfriend. And I
did feel I felt like I inspired her. I
felt like I won an Oscar, you know? Oh,
she's like, "To all the girls at home
watching, if you two just dream it to be
true, one day an okay guy will text you
back. Just keep dreaming, lady."
[applause and cheering]
It's like,
but I um I did it. I did it. I don't
know. I did it. I got a man. I'm I'm
shock. I got one. I got one. [laughter]
I'm
And I know I know that's a weird way to
phrase that. I know that's it's like
it's a weird way to say I got a man. It
sounds like I got a car, you know.
[laughter] He's fresh off the lot, used,
but good condition, you know. Strong
build, makes me feel safe.
It's true, though. He makes me feel
safe. It's a, you know, as a woman,
there's something very comforting when
you have a man you trust walk you down
the street at night. It feels very nice.
And when he walks me down the street, I
know he's protecting me. I know it. But
I I ask myself, what is he protecting me
from? [laughter]
Other men. So, what is this scam you
guys are running against us? This is the
longest running scam in human history.
Okay, for real. And everyone says just
learn self-defense. But I've looked up
the classes. They're all taught by men.
Okay. Is this a pyramid scheme?
[laughter] Is it a So, I'm paying a man
to teach me how to kick him in the
balls. He's like, "Here's how I would
attack you." I'm like, "What? Like,
what's it's just like [laughter]
it's a pyramid scheme, right? Is it like
how are you the problem and the
solution? [laughter]
I don't understand." [clears throat] But
it is I guess it is true what they say,
right ladies? The only way to stop a bad
guy with a dick is a good guy with a
dick. There you go. Yes. So, we got to
stay strapped in these streets. Find
that safe dong. [laughter] You'll f
Sorry, I pointed at it. I Sorry, but
you're good for You know what I
[laughter] mean?
I'm lucky. I I'm lucky I met this man.
He's uh he he's a catch, you know, but I
I'm lucky I met him. I'm just not uh
thrilled with the way we met. It's just
Hinge. That's it. Dating app. That's our
story. That's going to be our story. I
wanted something romantic, you know. But
it's Hinge. There's nothing romantic
about shopping online for a person.
[laughter]
That's all these all these apps are.
You're just shopping online for people.
And there's filters for you on these
apps like Amazon Prime. Very unsexy
filters. Just just the stats, you know?
It's like age, height, religion,
politics, kids, you know, and the least
the least romantic filter of them all is
the distance.
[laughter]
Where do you want your person? That's
this. But what this filter is really
asking you is how far would you go?
Right? It's like how bad do you want it,
son? And that's and on my on my hinge
distance, I put the maximum amount,
which people do laugh, but it worked. I
found the [\h__\h] Okay, it worked. I
found him. But I and I swiped but I
swiped for years, dude. I swiped for a
decade all through Southern California.
Like I I [\h__\h] my way all the way to
San Bernardino and back. Do you
understand? [laughter] I don't know why
I did the and back, but I was looking
for love. I was taking it seriously, but
I asked uh I thought it would be cute if
I asked my my man. I was like, "Honey,
what did you put on your your hinge
radius? How far were you willing to go
to find me?" But I forgot you're never
supposed to ask a question if you're not
ready to hear the answer. Do you know
what this [\h__\h] said to me? [laughter]
Five miles.
Five. Five. [laughter] I was like, "What
am I Uber Eats?
Okay. You can't just open up your phone
and be like, "No, I'm in the mood for
Asian. What's open near me?" Like,
yummy. [laughter] Like, this is my life.
Five miles. That was livid. Filled with
rage. 5 miles. Can I ask a question? Did
anyone here at this show travel more
than 5 miles to come see me tonight?
>> You did. You [applause] did. You did. I
will make love to each and every one of
you, okay? to prove HIM A POINT. OKAY,
[applause]
cuz I I don't do merch at my shows. I do
I do twoon-one hookups cuz we got to we
got to go to bed, right? [laughter] We
got to got to speed this up.
He's here, too. I love that. You hear
that? I'm [\h__\h] all of them, sweetie.
You hear that? Okay.
I [laughter]
But um you know, I I I don't I guess I
get it. I don't know. Five miles. It's
LA. It's a big city, but you know, LA,
it's LA is the best, right? There's so
much to do. It's an amazing city.
There's so much to explore. He loves to
find new fun things to do in LA. And I I
found out one day he
drove from Korea Town all the way to
Venice Beach [laughter]
for a sandwich.
[laughter] You would know how far that
is, right? You know that. You know that.
know how far 15 miles he traveled for
his one and only Mortadella on Fakatcha
his beautiful but for me for me
[laughter]
5.1 miles past
what does she come with a bag of Doritos
or something what am I driving six miles
for [laughter] you know
I'm just it's just not romantic that's
what makes me sad it's not it's not a
nice story cuz some of some of us met on
apps we might get older and we might
have kids together one day you know with
your person Your your kids are going to
ask you the story. They're going to want
to know. They're going to ask you like,
"Papa, [laughter] what's the what's the
first thing you noticed about mom?" You
know, like, "What are you what are you
going to say?" Like, "Well, she was
conveniently located. [laughter]
Took my breath away." You know what I
mean? It's not It's not It's not
romantic. It's not It's you know what?
They're going to ask you all these
questions like, "What what were you
doing when you first saw her? What were
you doing? What are you What are you
going to say?" Pooping. [laughter]
You were pooping. I was poop. Chipotle
was leaving your [\h__\h] and you saw I
saw your mom on a hike and a you know
and I thought Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. For
sure. For sure. Why not? You know what
[laughter] I mean? That's that's your
story. That's it. Okay.
You know, I want I wanted to work out
cuz he's like he he has a lot going for
him. He's an amazing person. He do he's
uh he's 6'2.
He's Brazilian.
Okay, back off, [\h__\h] Back off.
[laughter]
Remember, I [\h__\h] all the way to San.
Okay, just Okay, sorry.
That was a tick. That's a me problem,
not a you problem. Um,
[laughter]
but he's a he's a, you know, he's a hot
hot Brazilian man. He's um he does a lot
of stuff. That's good. He he he's in
therapy, [laughter] you know, right? He
works on himself, right? He's a good
man.
He uses face cream.
He does that. He does that on his own,
you know. I And I never taught him that.
Okay. He does that on his own. I when I
went to his bathroom, I saw all this
Neutrogena for the first time. I was
like, who is this moist king? I cannot
[laughter]
lose him. I can't lose him. And he's
slippery, right? He's slippery. So when
he runs, I'm [\h__\h] I really But I He's
so creamy. [snorts] I love to rub him. I
love [laughter]
He's so silky smooth. I love rubbing
him. She's so soft. And I know I know
how dramatic I sound when I talk about
this, but I've dated plenty of men who
didn't realize that lotion could go on
your face. They had no idea. Which I
find very interesting cuz I know you
guys use lotion. [laughter]
You use a lot of lotion. You use a lot
for one very special activity. You guys
are using lotion, right? And you guys
think we don't know. We know. Okay.
[laughter] We see those bottles all over
the house. All over the house. These
Kirkland ass bottles. [laughter] All
over the house. In every room. Every
room. I'm like the pantry. Jesus Christ,
dude. [laughter] In front of the
Teddygrams. Like really,
it's just I don't know. We know what's
going down cuz it's like I I'm no
detective. I I I see those lotion the
lotion's going down in those bottles and
your skin's still dry, right? So, riddle
me that. [laughter]
And it's like we've all we all know what
they look like, right? We've all seen
them. They're so shiny. They they
glisten. [laughter] They're so shiny,
right? We know where the lotion's going.
That's what I'm saying. It's just like
it's it's just like moderation when
you're down there. Just just next next
time you're down there, right? Just like
spread some up.
Spread it. Spread it [laughter] up and
pat some under the under eye. Like pat
pat pat with your cuz you have extra.
You always have extra. Just pat it here,
you know? Pat, [laughter] pat. Okay. I
don't know. But I love I love you guys.
I want I want you all to succeed. If I
could give you some advice, um if you
used more lotion here,
you wouldn't have to use as much
here. Do you do you understand?
Do you hear the women clapping? That's
data. [laughter]
That's science. Okay?
And think of me next time you cream
yourselves. Okay? [laughter] Will you
talk to me? I'm sorry.
>> Okay. Um,
should I have kids?
>> Jesus Christ. [laughter]
There. My man is in the crowd. You heard
that, sweetie? We're not. You know, it
is always women that say no. I I like
all around like I when I tour
everywhere, I go to all these cities.
It's a lot of women that tell me no.
It's like a bummer. They come up to me
after the shows. They're like, "Don't
don't [\h__\h] do it. Don't
>> [laughter]
>> You know, I'm like, "Let go my
shoulders, lady." Like, "Why are you
someone so aggressive?
I'm scared to have kids. Um, you know, I
what I think of is if you're a parent,
uh, what that means is you automatically
become like a hundred different things,
right? Like you're a parent, and then
all of a sudden you're a you're a chef,
you're a chauffeur, you're an assistant,
you're a therapist, you're a coach,
you're a teacher." That's what I'm
scared about. Like you you just become a
teacher. They look to you to learn
things, right? And like I know everyone
thinks it, but I'm not that smart. Okay.
Like I I'm very curious but not about
important things. Okay. Uh I have I have
YouTube. I have YouTube on my phone,
right? I have access to all the
information in the entire world, but I'm
not proud of what I'm typing [laughter]
in that search bar. What am I supposed
to teach my child when I tuck them in at
night? What am I going to say? What am I
going to teach them about? Like shutter
island ending explained.
[laughter]
That's all that's in here. What about
you know what I mean? I'm just tucking
him in like you you see Leo wasn't
trying to escape the island.
[laughter]
He was trying to escape his mind. Okay.
I know. I don't know how to talk about a
lot of stuff. I can't I can barely keep
up with like the news and current
events. You know what I mean? Like all
if you ever see me at a party silently
staring at a group of adults, just know
that I am waiting for someone to bring
up the movie. [laughter]
Shudder Island. That's all. I'm just
like staring at people's mouths like,
"What's Mark Ruffalo been up to lately?
Anyone?" [laughter]
Okay. I do love kids though. I love
kids. Like I'm an auntie and I I love
it. I love these kids. Are they They're
amazing. Are there do we have aunties or
uncles in here? It's great. Yeah. See,
we Yeah. See, we have energy. Aunties
and uncles, [cheering] we have energy
because we we see the parents. You guys
are like, "You're really in the thick of
it. You're doing hard work. You're
exhausted." And we're having a much
better time because, you know what I
mean? Cuz like we're just micro doing
whatever you're on, right? [laughter]
It's nice cuz it's like I don't want the
full trip. I just want a little hit,
right? Like I'm not trying to go blind
and see the devil. I just want a little
like I want to go to sleep tonight and
know it's all going to end tomorrow.
This horrible feeling. These kids
chasing me. Okay. I I do understand that
there's a big shift now. I I know that
people actively don't plan to have kids,
which is totally fair. If it doesn't
make sense for you, do what makes sense
for you. I just don't understand why
these people love to brag about their
decision. It's a very weird I always
hear the same argument from people who
don't want kids. It's always this like I
don't have kids so I can do anything in
the world I want. I'm like really? What
are you doing? [laughter]
What are you doing? What are you doing?
That's so cool. You're so busy. You know
what I mean? What do you What do you got
tomorrow? Pickle ball. You're not even
that good. [laughter]
You're an average pickle ball player.
You're too busy to have kids cuz you're
playing a a child's game. You're missing
shots like this low to the ground, you
know, every Sunday. That's but good on.
You know what I I just don't know why
they brag. It's interesting. I once
heard a guy say he said to me, "I took
two naps today." I'm like, "I wouldn't
say that out loud. Why are you telling
me this?" [laughter]
I'm nervous. Uh I'm nervous what like my
hypothetical kids what they're going to
go through, you know? Like I remember
being in school and like just trying to
be a confident person in school. I I'm
I'm scared they're going to go through
the same things as me. Like they I
remember in um third grade uh Mrs. Py's
class, we were learning about science
and the weather and she asked the entire
class. She was like, "Okay, class. Does
anyone know why the second floor is
always a little hotter than the first
floor?" And I shot my hand up cuz I
thought I I was like, "Yeah, I know.
It's cuz the second floor is closer to
the sun. No further questions."
[laughter]
And everybody laughed just like this.
Triggering me. Triggering. Everybody
laughed. Everyone like it. All the kids
in unison were like, "No,
it's because hot air rise." It I'm like,
"This was before Google, dude." You know
what I mean? What are you guys all
doing? Is everyone going to Kuman
without me? How do you all know hot air
rises? And I even Mrs. P was like, "What
the [\h__\h] are you talking about, Leslie?"
You know, but um I really am grateful
for all of you for coming tonight. This
is a very big deal for me. Like, if you
weren't here, I wouldn't have this job.
like this is my job now. So, it's huge
that you came out. Thank you for being
here and delaying your bedtime, you
know? I know. I don't want to [applause]
That's That's when you clap
like, "Thank you for seeing me. I am
ready for bed, [\h__\h] Thank you for
acknowledging me." That's when you clap.
The [\h__\h] Okay. [laughter] Anyways,
again, that's a me problem. Um, don't do
better help, guys. It doesn't work. Um,
[laughter]
seriously, it doesn't it doesn't work.
This is an anti- ad. It does not work.
does not work. Maybe obviously it
doesn't work. Maybe because as I'm I'm
paying $12.99 a month. I'm like, "Oh, I
wonder why it has no effect." [laughter]
Okay. And I obviously need therapy cuz
it's like I just hear about [\h__\h]
Better Help on podcasts, you know? I
clearly need therapy if I'm taking
marching orders from Dax Sheepard. Okay.
That's I [laughter] clearly need help.
This is actually Okay, this is a really
big deal for me this whole night. I
really appreciate everyone coming. Uh
this is my job now. like doing standup
is my [cheering]
show. It's huge for me. [applause] It's
It's huge for me that you all came out
to to the show in LA cuz I started here
in LA years ago and it was a hustle cuz
I at the time I had a full-time day job
like office job. You guys go to the
office for your jobs.
>> Yeah. It's it's abuse. It's not right.
You know, [laughter] you're grown
adults. You go to the sad building and
pretend to work all day. You know, cuz
cuz you have a we have full-time jobs,
but none of you work the whole full
time. You know, we all had the same
schedule. I did the same thing. We all
work for 1 hour. You know, you commit.
You commit to the hour and then for 7
hours. It's makeelieve. It's [laughter]
pretend time. You just make [\h__\h] up. I
don't even know what my job was. I made
it up every day. Okay? And I get that
this is, you know, there's a stage and a
mic and everything. This looks like a
performance, but I promise you I
performed way harder at that office.
[laughter]
Every day I just if my boss walked by, I
would just pick up my phone. It wouldn't
even ring. I'd be like [laughter]
I'd be like, "We don't have the
BANDWIDTH FOR THAT." LIKE LIKE shovel
drawers just make [\h__\h] up. You know, if
she just walked by, I would just open up
a blank word dock AND TYPE SYNERGY
SYNERGY SYNERGY. [laughter]
That's all all I did. Okay.
But this was years ago. I So I I worked
all day in the office and I would go uh
straight to comedy clubs at night,
straight after work. So I would always
get ready for shows in my car. Like I
had all of my stuff in my car. And one
night my car was broken into. And they
stole three things. I'm going to say the
three things and I'll let you all guess
which one pissed me off the most. Okay.
[laughter]
They took my laptop,
>> all of my makeup,
and my joke notebook.
>> I don't like that a man said makeup. And
he WAS RIGHT. HE WAS RIGHT. HE
[laughter] WAS RIGHT. LIKE, YEAH, YOU
SEEM LIKE YOU'D BE PRETTY UPSET about
that. It was the makeup, my love. It was
the make it was the makeup. It was the
makeup. I went straight to the police
station crying, screaming, panicking,
you know? I was freaking out. THEY WERE
LIKE, "SIR, STAND BACK, SIR." CUZ I had
no makeup. I WAS LIKE,
THEY TOOK EVERYTHING. [laughter]
THEY'RE LIKE, "SIR, WAR YOUR VOICE." YOU
KNOW, [laughter] I told I told them it
was identity theft. That's what I
They're like, "Sir, THIS IS NOT IDENTITY
THEFT. WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?" I
was like, "Well, someone stole my face
in my jokes. So, what do you call that?
What do you file that under, officer?"
Okay, they stole it. Okay. [laughter]
But luckily on uh uh on this joke
notebook, I wrote my name and number. So
I got a text from a man named Evan who
who claimed he didn't take it. He said
he found my notebook. He was like, "Oh
yeah, I found your notebook. It was um
it was really easy to spot. It was on
Sunset Boulevard and it was sitting on
top of like all this really cheap
drugstore makeup." I [laughter] was
like, "SHUT THE [\h__\h] UP, EVAN. What are
you talking about? What? Like E.L.F. is
a nice brand. Are you What are you
kidding me? $8 concealer in this
economy. You [\h__\h] with elf. You [\h__\h]
with me, dude. What are you talking
about? [laughter]
That's
He's doesn't even know me. He's roasting
me, dude. [laughter]
You know, and I when he told me that my
makeup was on the streets, like
obviously whoever broke into my car
didn't take my makeup, but they they
must have seen it and had an impression
of me, you know. They saw they saw all
these like fake lashes and contour kits.
[laughter] They were like, "Wow, this
drag queen is really on the go.
He needs to rest, [laughter] you know.
You know,
but uh you know, at the time this guy
Evan didn't know that I did standup and
he read my entire joke notebook and he
didn't find it very funny, right? He he
told me so. He read the entire joke
notebook and he thought my joke notebook
was a sad autobiographical screenplay
[laughter] about a lonely lady in LA who
couldn't find love. He was like giving
me notes. He was texting me notes every
night on my screenplay. She's like, he's
like, "Yeah, the main character, she's
clearly broken [laughter]
and selfish, you know." I was like, "I
think she's doing just fine." All right.
[laughter]
Okay, guys. Let's go to bed. That's all
for me. Thank you [cheering]
so much. Go to sleep.
Thank you.
HEAT. HEAT.
[cheering]
[applause]
[music]